(Amy:)Wow, my boyfriend is friends
with Stephen Hawking...
(Amy:)...and my new dandruff shampoo
doesn't smell like tar.
(Amy:)Everything really is coming up Amy.
(Sheldon:)It is glorious.
(Sheldon:)One of the greatest intellects
of our time...
(Sheldon:)...has agreed to engage with me
in a gentlemanly battle of wits.
(Sheldon:)And I'm spanking him so hard, his grad
students won't be able to sit down.
(Amy:)You know, when one male dominates
another, his testosterone level rises.
- What's your point?
- It's exciting to think...
(Amy:)...you might be getting
a testosterone level.
Ooh! My friend Stephen just played
the word "act" for 18 points.
(Sheldon:)That's right, I call him Stephen now.
(Sheldon:)Because I checked,
and he was not okay with Wheels.
Oh. You could turn his "act" into "extract"...
(Amy:)...and it would be for double points.
(Sheldon:)Amy, why would you give me a word?